躲猫猫  找到你啦
Peek-a-boo. I see you.
耶耶耶
Yeah yeah yeah.
噢  躲猫猫
Oh. Peek-a-boo.
又找到你啦
I see you.
好的
Yeah.
准备好了吗
Ready ready?
躲猫猫  找到你啦
Peek-a-boo! I see you.
这游戏永远没有结束的时候
I just realized there's no end to this game.
哦吼
Woo-hoo!
我猜猜发生什么了
Let me guess.
你又要上电视了是么
You're gonna be on TV again.
哦  太难以置信了
Oh! I can't believe it.
是《早安丹佛》节目组
"Good Morning, Denver" Called.
他们想让我再录一期节目
They want me to do another segment.
真的  上次都那样子了
Really? After what happened last time?
没错  事实证明  房屋倒塌收视率不错
Yeah. Turns out, a house falling down is actually good TV.
现在的问题是  我要如何占据收视榜首
Question is, how am I gonna top it?
好的  老妈  我也有个好消息
Okay, mom. I have some good news too.
-真的吗  什么事呀  -简直太激动了
- Oh really? What's going on? - This is so exciting.
你知道耶鲁是我的大学首选嘛
So you know how Yale is my first choice of colleges?
对啊
Yeah.
耶鲁为我安排了一次校友面试
They've scheduled an alumni
就在这里  在我们家
interview for me right here at the house.
那个  这不是说我肯定能被录取
I mean, it doesn't mean that I'm in for sure,
但是这的确说明他们对我很感兴趣
but it definitely means that they're interested.
面试顺利的话  绝对大大加分啊
And if it goes well, it's a really big plus.
太好了
That's great.
你有在听吗
You having trouble focusing?
我要上电视了
I'm gonna be on TV.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late and dad jokes.
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
"Has anybody seen my left shoe?"
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
■
翻译： 寂_翼  苏赛崽
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud.
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
There it is up on the roof.
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I survived.
■
校订： Enpistu
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice.
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby
■
后期： Enpistu  liloelva
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy.
可是我知道你会有美好将来
But I know your future's bright.
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby
不要怀疑
There's no maybe.
一切终会如你所愿
Everything turns out all right.
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down.
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back around.
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be.
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby.
查莉成长日记  第四季第三集
Good Luck Charlie  S04E03  Demolition Dabney
你去开门不
You want to get that?
和人打交道不是我的菜  你去吧
And interact with people? No thanks.
-嗨  -嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
我是劳伦  新来的邻居
I'm Lauren. I'm new to the
我正在找看孩子的工作
neighborhood and I'm looking for babysitting jobs.
我听说你们家有很多小孩
And I heard you guys have lots of babies.
哦  确实如此
Oh, that we do.
这也表明我们不缺免费看孩子的人手
But it also means that I have a lot of free babysitters.
老爸老爸老爸
Dad dad dad.
我们的人选可以更多样一些嘛
Shouldn't we keep our options open?
-你好  我是盖比  -嗨  劳伦
- Hi. I'm Gabe. - Hi. I'm Lauren.
我觉得该给她安排个面试
I probably should interview her
确保她是满足我们高标准的人才
just to make sure she meets our high standards.
不是谁都可以照顾我们的  呃
Can't just let anybody babysit for, uh...
-托比  -托比  对
- Toby? - Toby, right. Yeah.
多谢提醒
Thank you.
好的  劳伦  你做看孩子的工作有多久了
So, Lauren, how long have you been babysitting?
差不多一年吧
About a year.
嗯  好的
Okay. All right.
下一个问题  你有男朋友了么
Follow-up question. Do you have a boyfriend?
这和看孩子有什么关系吗
What does that have to do with babysitting?
哦  我在看你能否胜任别的工作
Oh, I'm interviewing for something else now.
哦
Oh.
这样的话  我还没有呢
In that case, I don't have a boyfriend.
你呢  有女朋友了吗
Do you have a girlfriend?
我正在努力
I'm working on it.
你真可爱
You're cute.
确实  不是吗
I am, aren't I?
对了  你是刚来到这个社区的是吗
So, you're new to the neighborhood, huh?
对  我要在这里和外婆住一段时间
Yeah, I'm staying with my grandmother for a while.
我真想去拜访她一下
I can't wait to meet her.
你早就拜访过了
You already have.
哦  不是吧
Oh no!
哦  就是呢
Oh yes.
走吧  劳伦  这家伙就是我警告过你的那个
Let's go, Lauren. This is the one I warned you about.
他是那个恶魔男孩
This is the Devil Child?
但他看上去人畜无害
But he seems so nice.
所以才说他是恶魔啊
That's what makes him the Devil Child.
嘿  人总会变的
Hey, people change.
-哦  嘿  PJ  -嘿  老妹
- Oh, hey, PJ. - Hey, sis.
那个  我有个问题要问你
So, I have a question for you.
明天下午三点你打算去哪里
Where are you going to be tomorrow at 3:00 pm?
我准备好了个答案给你
Now I have an answer for you.
除了这里哪儿都行
Anywhere but here.
为什么不能待在家里
Why can't I be here?
因为有个耶鲁的人要来面试我
Because a guy is coming over to interview me for Yale,
我希望家里只有我
and so I want the house to myself.
你觉得我会丢脸是么
Because you're ashamed of me?
不只是你  家里所有人
Not just of you. Everybody.
哦  好吧  这样还好受一点
Oh. Well, that makes me feel a little better.
行  我想我明天不会呆在家里了
All right. I guess I can not be here tomorrow.
太好了  谢啦
Great. Thanks.
噢  明天三点有我最喜欢的卡通呢好想看
Oh, although I was gonna watch my cartoons tomorrow at 3:00.
一天不看又不会怎样
Can't you just skip a day?
大学面试不参加又不会怎样
Can't you just skip your college interview?
你的事情就比我的重要了么
Why is your stuff more important than mine?
我那可是耶鲁
Because mine involves Yale,
你的就是一个拎手提箱的乌龟
and yours involves a turtle with a suitcase.
拎的是公文包  而且那是进入异世界的大门
It's a briefcase, and it's a portal to another dimension.
求你了  明天千万别出现在家里
I'm begging you. Please don't be here tomorrow.
好吧  我做点别的事情
All right. I'll make other arrangements.
太谢谢了
Thank you.
耶鲁大学的面试
Got an interview for Yale.
快点长大吧丫头
Grow up.
嘿
Hey.
嘿  看看是谁来啦
Hey. What do we have here?
嗯  终于有一个孩子想要来看看她老爸工作的地方了
Well, one of my kids finally wanted to see where daddy works.
那么  小查莉  觉得怎么样呀
So, Charlie, what do you think?
我们可以走了吗
Can we go now?
查莉  我们才刚到啊
Charlie, we just got here.
哦
Oh.
要不要坐坐老爸的工作椅
You want to sit in daddy's chair?
会转的哟
It spins around.
-好吧  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
-下一个我能来玩么  老板  -我们已经玩够了  弗恩
- Can I go next, boss? - We've been over this, Vern.
好的  看看我们今天的工作行程是什么
So, what have we got lined up for today?
和昨天一样  无事
Same as yesterday. Nothing.
什么  伙计  这
What? Man, what...
我不懂了
I don't get it.
为什么生意这么萧条  我们都换上新广告了啊
Why is business down? I mean, we just put out new advertising.
快看  查莉
Charlie, look.
嗯
Huh?
-你觉得怎么样  -好吓人啊爸爸
- What do you think? - That's scary, daddy.
哪里吓人了  多有才啊
It's not scary. It's clever.
哦  你还不识字呢
Oh, you just can't read yet.
所以你不知道那是个双关语  你看哈
You don't realize this is a pun, see?
爸爸穿得像一个拳击手
Daddy's all dressed up like a boxer.
我将要击倒你全部的害虫问题
So I'm gonna knock out your bug problems.
击倒东西  拳击手总是这样做的
Boxers knock things out.
啊  太有才了
Oh, that is clever.
-PJ  在想什么呢  -我有个严峻的问题
- PJ, what you thinking about? - I've got a problem.
我必须找到一个地方
I'm trying to figure out
好在明天下午三点看我的卡通片
where to watch my cartoons tomorrow at 3:00.
你的公寓不行么
How about your place?
不  埃米特那时候要看他的卡通片
No, because Emmett's gonna be watching his cartoons then.
呵呵  原来别人的问题
Boy, you think you have a
都是这样容易解决的啊
problem then you hear something like that.
你有什么问题么
What's your problem?
呃  我喜欢上了一个女孩
Well, I like this girl,
但是她的外婆是达布尼太太
but it turns out her grandmother's Mrs. Dabney.
-天啊  那真惨  -对啊
- Ooh. Oh. That is bad. - Yeah.
通常来说  知道谁和她有关系的话
Normally, I'd have nothing
我都离得远远的
to do with anyone related to Dabney but,
但是那是劳伦  她身上
Lauren has that one quality
有其他女孩身上不曾具有的特质
I've never really found in a girl before.
-什么  -她喜欢我
- What's that? - She likes me.
听起来确实不错啊伙计  加油吧少年
Sounds like one of a kind, man. You should go for it.
你知道吗  你是对的  没什么大不了的
You know what? You're right. Here goes nothing.
嘿  你去那边顺便问下达布尼太太
Oh hey, while you're there, will you find out if Mrs. D will be
她明天下午三点会看《小鸭子雅克》么
watching "Yacky the Duck" Tomorrow at 3:00?
-劳伦在么  -在
- Is Lauren here? - Yes.
我能找她一下么
Can I see her?
有什么事
About what?
那是我和她之间的事情
That's between me and her.
那么现在在你和她之间的正是我
Right now what's between you and her is me.
所以有话就快说
So start talking.
-嗨  盖比  -嘿  劳伦
- Hi, Gabe. - Hey, Lauren.
明天要不要一起去滑旱冰
Do you want to go roller skating tomorrow?
可以吗  外婆
Can I, grandma?
现在是我的事情了吧
And now it's back to me.
拜托拜托
Pretty please?
噢  好吧
Oh, all right.
-谢谢外婆  -太棒了
- Thanks. - Yes.
你什么时候来接我们
What time will you be picking us up?
你们
Us?
没有监护人陪伴我可不能让你俩出去
Well, I'm not gonna let you two go unchaperoned.
约我外孙女  等同约我
You date her, you date me.
好吧  我明天下午一点来
Fine. I'll be by tomorrow around 1:00.
你会顺便带我们去吃顿干酪汉堡么
Will you be taking us out for cheeseburgers?
别逼我
Don't push it.
打扮得帅一点哦
Wear something cute.
-早上好啊  弗恩  -看我发现了什么
- Good morning, Vern. - Look what I found.
旧的那个我
The old me.
大男孩鲍伯  休息室这帮人总这么称呼他
Big boy Bob, as the guys in the break room used to say.
休息室里就只有我们俩  弗恩
The only guys in the break room are you and me, Vern.
好吧那可能只是我这么觉得
I guess I said it to myself.
干嘛把他拿出来
Why is he here?
嗯  我一直在想
Well, I've been thinking.
我们以前活儿很多的
We used to get a lot of
那时候公司形象是他
jobs when this guy was the face of the company.
但是然后呢
But then...
这个家伙来了
This guy came along.
正如你家小丫头说的  他很吓人
And as your little girl said, he's scary.
但他也很有型啊
He's also in shape.
我觉得是新鲍伯把顾客吓跑的
I think the new Bob is frightening the customers.
你会希望这个鲍伯在你家里
This guy you want in your house.
和蔼可亲  惹人喜爱  他可能会吃点饼干
He's warm, he's cuddly, he's gonna eat some cookies,
甚至在你家沙发上小睡一会
maybe take a nap on your couch.
我就那样做过一次
I only did that once.
而这个鲍伯呢  他很严肃  很有威慑力
But this guy, he's tough, he's menacing,
他看上去会灭掉害虫  但是之后呢
he's gonna kill the bugs, but then what?
他嗜血的欲望还没得到满足
Now he's got a taste for blood.
太荒唐  你这是说什么  维恩
Oh, that's ridic... what are you saying, Vern?
你想让我再胖回去吗
You want me to put the weight back on?
哦不  当然不是
Oh no no. Of course not.
没人这么说
Nobody's saying anything like that.
不是的
No no.
哦  看这儿
Oh, lookie here.
一个吃到饱为止的自助餐广告
An ad for an all-you-can-eat buffet.
不过和我们一点关系都没有哎
And us with nothing to do.
没问题
Okay.
你好  我是莱昂内尔·凡·奈斯  耶鲁85届校友
Hello. I'm Lionel Van Ness. Yale '85.
你好  我是泰迪·邓肯
Hi. I'm Teddy Duncan.
耶鲁18岁校友  如果一切顺利的话
Yale '18. If all goes well.
能从头来过么
Can we start over?
你好  我是莱昂内尔·凡·奈斯  耶鲁85届校友
Hello. I'm Lionel Van Ness. Yale '85.
请进  随意点就好
Please, make yourself comfortable.
好的  我知道这种面试可能会有些压迫感
Listen, I know these interviews can be intimidating,
但是我希望你放松下来展示最真实的自己
but I just want you to relax, be yourself.
我们只是随意的交谈
We're just two people talking.
听起来不错
Sounds good to me.
那么  泰迪  你为什么选择耶鲁呢
So, Teddy, what made you think about Yale?
那个  原因很多
Oh well, there are so many reasons.
如果一定要我选择一个的话
But if I had to pick one,
大概是因为我喜欢斗牛犬吧
I guess I'd say I have a thing for bulldogs.
那是吉祥物
It's the mascot.
嗨  这里在干嘛
Oh, hi. What's going on here?
我告诉过你  我的大学面试
I told you. My college interview.
哦  对  不好意思
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
我是艾米·邓肯  泰迪的妈妈
I'm Amy Duncan. Teddy's mom.
你好啊  我是莱昂内尔·凡·奈斯
Hello, Lionel Van Ness.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
妈妈  你在干嘛呢
Uh, mom, what are you doing?
我在旁听
I'm sitting in.
你甚至发觉不了我在这里的
You won't even know that I'm here.
你应该没什么问题吧  莱昂内尔
That's all right with you, isn't it, Lionel?
好吧  这虽然有点不太寻常  但是还行吧
Well, it's a bit unusual, but I guess it's okay.
太好了  过来吧  男孩子们
Great. Come on in, boys.
这是在干什么
What is going on?
现在让我们回到
Okay, let's go back to where
你们好像第一次见面的时候  好吗
you greet each other like you never met, okay?
调好状态
And with good energy.
这都是什么啊
What is all this?
哦  对不起  莱昂内尔  我来解释一下
Oh, I'm sorry, Lionel. Allow me to explain.
我是个当地电视界的名人
I'm a local TV personality.
我正在拍我的节目《早安丹佛》中的一段
And I'm filming a segment for my show "Good Morning, Denver".
然后你们俩会参与其中哦
And you two are gonna be on it.
不  我们不要
No, we're not.
我亲爱的小泰迪  她这么美丽动人
My sweet Teddy. She's so beautiful,
真不敢相信她面对镜头会害羞
it's hard to believe she's camera shy.
妈  我们俩能不能去厨房小谈一下
Mom, could I have a quick word with you in the kitchen?
-没问题  宝贝  -好的 一会儿回来
- Sure, Sweetie. - Yes. Be right back.
肯  你能不能给他换一件上衣呀
Hey Ken, could you get him into a different shirt?
要和我的眼睛很相配
One that goes with my eyes?
-你在干嘛啊  -我在一箭双雕一石二鸟啊
- What are you doing?! - I'm killing two birds with one stone.
泰迪  我需要给节目新录一段内容
Teddy, I need a new segment for my show,
而且你需要我帮你进耶鲁大学
and you need help getting into Yale.
妈  这怎么会有帮助呢
Mom, how is this helping?
在电视上面试会让你脱颖而出的
Having your interview on TV is gonna make you stand out.
而且如果我也能获得
And if I happen to win a
一个本地艾美奖  这真是个双赢啊
local emmy as well, well, it's a win-win.
妈  这对我来说真的很重要
Mom, this is really important to me,
求您千万别给我弄砸了
so just please don't blow it.
我才不会弄砸了  好吗  我只需要五分钟
I'm not gonna blow it, okay? I just need five minutes.
快速拍一组镜头  我就撤
I'll get a couple of quick shots and I'll be on my way.
五分钟  就五分钟
Five minutes, but that's it.
谢谢亲爱的  等一下等一下
Thank you, honey. Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa.
还有一件事
One more thing, if you could
如果你能找到一些机会
find some time to mention the phrase um...
提到“瑞克的餐厅  尝得到的品质”的话
"Rick's Diner, quality you can taste"...
那就  要求太多了  就这样吧
that would be... too much? Okay.
我们现在还玩的挺好的对吧
So. We having fun yet?
-不好  -太好了
- No. - Good.
嘿  伙计们
Oh, hey, guys.
PJ  你来这里干嘛啊
PJ! What the heck are you doing here?
来溜冰场  好意外啊
At the roller rink unexpectedly.
哦  嗨  盖比
Oh, hello, Gabe.
我就是来溜冰的
I just came by to roller skate.
像每一天的这个时候一样
As I often do this time of day.
既然你来了  你就能当我们监护人了
As long as you're here, you can chaperone us,
达布尼夫人就可以回家了
and Mrs. Dabney can go home.
你真以为我会把我孙女留给恶魔小孩
Do you really think I'd leave my granddaughter with Devil Child
和恶魔小孩他笨蛋哥哥吗
and Devil Child's dimwitted brother?
不用担心  达布尼夫人  我和盖比也会在这里的
Don't worry, Mrs. Dabney. Gabe and I will be here too.
好吧  新计划  你来拖住达布尼
Okay, new plan. You keep Dabney
这样我就有时间单独和劳伦相处了
occupied so I can get some alone time with Lauren.
-没问题的弟弟  -谢谢了
- Alright you got it little bro. - Thanks.
我不会让达布尼夫人离开我的视线的
I will not let Mrs. Dabney out of my sight.
我把她看丢了
I lost her.
-太棒了  是吧  -嗯
- This is nice, huh? - Yeah.
哦  我想这是个成对的组合
Oh, I think it's a couples' skate.
所以  我们应该要牵起手来了
So I think we're supposed to hold hands.
好吧  如果我们必须要的话
Well, if we have to.
如果我们必须要的话
If we have to.
你不必了
Oh no you don't.
现在是滑冰三人组了
And now it's triple skate.
找到她啦
Found her.
此外  我对写作非常有兴趣
Also, I've always been interested in writing,
我知道耶鲁大学有个非常不错的英语系
and I know that Yale has a great English Department which, um...
那是首先吸引我的地方
Is actually what drew me there in the first place.
你知道  我打算做一名记者  或者
You know, I've considered a career in... in journalism and possibly...
教书  你的气都喘到我脖子上来了
Teaching. You're breathing on my neck.
亲爱的  这都是为了镜头  这叫双人特写镜头
Honey, it's for the camera. It's called a two-shot.
你拍到了吗  肯
Are you getting this, Ken?
你对自己最大的挑战是怎么想的
What would you consider your greatest challenge?
哦  你是说除了这个吗
Oh, you mean besides this?
我想我要说的是  选择正确的专业
I have to say choosing the right major.
因为我有很多不同的兴趣爱好
Because I have so many different interests.
-那将会  -如果是我的话  莱昂内尔
- It's gonna... - You know, if I may, Lionel.
我觉得泰迪想说的是
I think what Teddy's trying to say is that,
她之所以想去耶鲁大学是因为
she has been drawn to Yale because
她想跟随她妈妈的步伐
she wants to follow in her mother's footsteps.
哦  您也读过耶鲁大学吗
Oh, did you go to Yale?
我想去来着
I thought about it.
后来我选择了丹佛西南社区学院
But then I chose Southwest Denver Community College.
落基山脉的瑰宝
The jewel of The Rockies.
你懂的  耶鲁都快被人讲烂了
You know, Yale's just been done to death, so.
说回到泰迪  呃  给我讲讲你的课余活动吧
Getting back to Teddy uh, tell me about your extracurriculars.
嗯  我一直很热爱戏剧
Uh, well, I've always had a passion for theater.
-它很  -我有个问题
- It's... - I have a question.
肯  你要跟紧了
You're gonna want to go tight on this, Ken.
作为一个关心你的妈妈  我想了解一下你的午餐计划
As a concerned mother, I want to know about your meal plan.
我才不要把我的宝贝女儿送到那么远的地方
I am not gonna send my daughter all the way across the country
如果她没有均衡的营养做支柱的话
if she doesn't have balanced nutrition and...
不好意思  我能做得更好的  我们再来一遍吧
I'm sorry. I can do so much better. Let's just do that again.
-作为一个关心她的  -打住
- As a concerned... - Stop it!
-怎么了  -你的五分钟时间到了
- What? - Your five minutes are up.
你们完工了
You're done.
-泰迪  我在试着帮你  -谁
- Teddy, I'm just trying to help. - Who?
你在帮谁  这都不是我了
Who are you helping? Because it's not me.
伙计们  能不能先关一下摄像机  就五分钟
Guys, could you turn the camera off. Just take five.
我又这样了  是不是
I did it again, didn't I?
对不起啊  泰迪  真对不起
I'm sorry, Teddy. I'm so so sorry.
我只是  有些时候
I just... sometimes I
我太想上电视了  我都失去理智了
want to be on TV so bad that I lose my head.
好吧  都结束了
Yeah, well, it's over.
凡奈斯先生  我
So Mr. Van Ness, I'm...
非常抱歉  浪费您的时间了
Very sorry that we wasted your time.
我知道  整个事情变成了一场灾难
I know this thing has been a complete disaster.
我也不可能去耶鲁了
And I'm never going to Yale.
事实上  你给我留下了非常深刻的印象
Actually, I'm very impressed with you.
你很优秀  很多才多艺
Your grades are excellent, you're well-rounded,
你不管遇到多么复杂的情形
and now that I know you've accomplished everything
也能镇静的面对
under such difficult circumstances...
我会推荐你的
I'm gonna recommend you.
真的吗
Really?
天啊  太棒了
Well, that's amazing!
不客气
You're welcome!
-怎么了  老大  -我们在拍照片  弗恩
- What's going on, boss? - We're doing a photo shoot, Vern.
哦  我们终于要拍照片日历了
Oh, we're finally gonna do that calendar?
鲍伯杀虫一扫光的男人
"The men of Bob's Bugs Be Gone".
新年宝宝我定了
Dibs on baby new year.
得给我一分钟让我忘掉那个画面
Yeah, I'm gonna need a minute to get that image out of my head.
不是啊  我考虑了你说的话
No, I was thinking about what you said.
关于顾客说我很吓人的那些
About how the customers think I'm scary.
-想了些什么  -可能你是对的
- What about it? - Maybe you're right.
所以你知道吗  我们要拍些新照片了
So you know what? We should do new shots.
让我看起来更友善可亲一些
Make me look friendly and lovable,
这样人们就愿意让我去他们家杀虫了
so that people will want me in their house killing things.
太棒了  咱们开始吧
Brilliant. Let's do it.
超超超级巨星
S-s-super star.
大明星  你来啦
Big star going far, there you are.
超超超级巨星
S-s-super star.
既然如此光鲜  就要活在当下  整晚洒脱狂欢
Look so bright. Livin' right. Here all night.
超超超级巨星
S-s-superstar.
这没用的 对吗
This isn't working, is it?
真遗憾  你没有小狗
Too bad you don't have a puppy.
对小萌物  没人会有抵抗力
Nobody can resist those little guys.
等一下  等一下  我有更好的
Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute. I got something even better.
这才像话嘛  老大
Now we're talking, boss.
嘿  我甚至想了一句新口号
Hey, I even have a new slogan.
我对待你的房子  恰如对待我的孩子
"I'll protect your house just like it's my own baby".
我喜欢
Love it.
我看起来怎么样
So how do I look?
-微笑如何  -一切都是我想要的
- Getting my smile okay? - I'm getting everything I need.
哇哦
Oh wow.
我都忘了约会有多好玩了
I forgot how much fun dating can be.
如果你再约我们出来的话  我们应该会答应的啦
If you ask us out again, we'll probably say yes.
好啊  达布尼太太  让我看看你都有什么本事
All right, Mrs. Dabney, let's see what you got.
不  我只有看着这俩人的本事
Oh no. I gotta keep my eye on these two.
哦  我懂了  你什么绝技也没有啊
Oh, I get it. You don't got any moves.
哦  拿这句等着我呢  是吧
Oh, it's gonna be like that, huh? All right.
你们俩  自己好好玩
You two, hands to yourself.
我得带PJ去学校
I gotta take PJ to school.
-走吧  -好的
- Let's go. - Okay.
哇哦  达布尼太太  你的绝技还真不错
Wow, Mrs. Dabney, you move pretty well for an old...
对一个老滑冰选手来说
School skater.
你为什么暂停呢
Why did you pause?
我
I...
有时会这样
Sometimes do that.
你知道吗  我曾经参加过一个滑冰比赛
You know, I was once in an ice skating contest
我抱起盖比  让他在我头顶转了两圈
where I picked Gabe up and twirled him over my head.
这不会发生在咱俩身上的
Not gonna happen.
哦  我和重力原理都不会允许的
Oh, neither I nor the laws of gravity were suggesting it.
有时候你很聪明  有时候你又很笨
Sometimes you're smart, sometimes you're dumb.
很难保持的啦
It's hard to keep up.
我只是想让你知道
I just want you to know
不管你奶奶说了些什么
that no matter what your grandmother says,
我不是个坏男孩
I'm not a bad guy.
也许我喜欢坏男孩呢
Maybe I like bad guys.
-准备好更上一层楼了吗  -谁都别拦着我
- Ready to kick it up a notch? - Try and stop me!
不
No!
嘿  查莉  一些小建议
Hey, Charlie. So piece of advice,
等你大学面试的时候  你就过去面试吧
when it's time for your college interviews, just go to them.
别让他们来家找你
Don't let them come to you.
你知道吗  其实呢  这个道理适用于很多情况
You know what? Actually, this applies to everything.
玩乐的约会啊  过夜的狂欢啊  第一次约会啊
Playdates, sleepovers, first dates.
基本上  所有的社交活动吧
Basically any social interaction.
你能去别的地方拍这个吗  我这儿正受伤
Can you do that somewhere else? I'm hurting over here.
盖比很暴躁
Gabe's a little cranky.
他去约会了  遭遇了一点小事故
He went on a date and had a little mishap.
小事故吗
A mishap?
我出去寻找真爱  达布尼太太却迎面而来
I went looking for love and got a face full of Dabney.
祝他好运吧  小查莉
Wish him good luck, Charlie.
躲猫猫  我看见你啦
Peek-a-boo. I see you.
Peek-a-boo! I see you.
天啊  这游戏我真玩腻了
Man, I'm so sick of this game.
这家伙还挺喜欢玩的
And this guy seems to love it.
躲猫猫  我看见你啦
Peek-a-boo. I see you.
哦  来玩个新的啊
Oh, there's a new twist...
还是没有
Not.
躲猫猫  我看见你啦
Peek-a-boo! I see you.
什么都行  除了这个
Anything but this.
公车的轮子  可爱的小蜘蛛  或者其他什么都行
"Wheels on the bus"? "Itsy bitsy spider"? Something?
（注：美国著名童谣）
躲猫猫  我看见你啦
Peek-a-boo. I see you.
求您啦
Check, please?!
三点啦
3 o'clock.
《小鸭子雅克》时间
Time for "Yacky the Duck".
谢天谢地
Oh, thank goodness.
哦  这集我看过了
Oh, I've seen this one already.
啊  别啊别啊  值得再看一遍的
Huh? No no no no no. It's worth another look.
还是有一些小小的  细微的差别的
There's nuance, subtlety, there's...
躲猫猫  我看见你啦
Peek-a-boo. I see you.
啊啊啊啊啊啊
Oh, Aah!